[
  {
    "number": 1,
    "questionId": "37c40592-fec9-4028-b780-72fea45a3549",
    "question": "Joints shall be brazed within how many hours after surfaces are cleaned for brazing?",
    "answer": "8 hours"
  },
  {
    "number": 2,
    "questionId": "92288a18-6d7b-41c0-9f7c-2a3564e87783",
    "question": "In what risk category is the loss of piped medical gas likely to cause minor injury?",
    "answer": "Category 2"
  },
  {
    "number": 3,
    "questionId": "bf710994-865f-4b8e-b15a-ccbbc2afe078",
    "question": "What is the purpose of the master alarm system in a medical gas setup?",
    "answer": "To monitor the operation and condition of the source of the supply, the reserver source (if any), and the pressure in the main lines of each medical gas and vacuum system"
  },
  {
    "number": 4,
    "questionId": "ec4055eb-2272-4e9b-87d3-faf7043f9218",
    "question": "What type of alarm is activated when the backup producer in a WAGD source system is running?",
    "answer": "Local Alarm"
  },
  {
    "number": 5,
    "questionId": "f7208564-55b0-4a41-9c1b-87209550d47f",
    "question": "The vacuum exhaust must discharge a minimum of how many feet from any building door, window, or air intake?",
    "answer": "25",
    "code_section": "5.1.3.7.7.2"
  },
  {
    "number": 6,
    "questionId": "fb92503a-adf2-4939-9c8c-dd585ca45496",
    "question": "Where instrument air systems are provided with a standby header, the header shall have how many cylinders attached?",
    "answer": "A sufficient amount for ONE hour of normal operation",
    "code_section": "5.1.13.3.7.6"
  },
  {
    "number": 7,
    "questionId": "37a2b646-7281-45f1-8a8c-dcc9672e7ad1",
    "question": "How should relief valve vent lines be labeled when vented to the outside?",
    "answer": "Any manner that will distinguish them from the medical gas pipeline"
  },
  {
    "number": 8,
    "questionId": "37f8aaeb-4db3-4809-9a35-0319c42b179d",
    "question": "What shall be used to label medical gas, medical support gas, and vacuum systems piping?",
    "answer": "stenciling or adhesive markers",
    "code_section": "5.1.11.1.1"
  },
  {
    "number": 9,
    "questionId": "5d181f31-57d0-4bc4-85e1-5af5bedaf01b",
    "question": "Which areas may require zone valves to be secured to prevent inappropriate access?",
    "answer": "psychiatric or pediatric areas",
    "code_section": "5.1.4.1.4"
  },
  {
    "number": 10,
    "questionId": "310e2719-fa8b-458e-86a1-f40948fbbd7e",
    "question": "Category 1 medical-surgical vacuum sources must consist of a minimum of how many vacuum pumps?",
    "answer": "2",
    "code_section": "5.1.3.7.1.1"
  },
  {
    "number": 11,
    "questionId": "fca636d4-4d76-4542-aee4-a4c5883a6634",
    "question": "The factory installed tuning on station outlets and inlets shall extend no further than how many inches from the body of the terminal?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "number": 12,
    "questionId": "b02cd6f8-971a-4a61-b7ae-98eb05a7ec23",
    "question": "The medical air intake must be located a minimum of how many feet from exhausts, fuel storage, or areas that can collect vehicle exhaust or other noxious fumes?",
    "answer": "25 ft",
    "code_section": "5.1.3.6.3.11"
  },
  {
    "number": 13,
    "questionId": "655f36cd-a9b1-4fb7-9b11-50263b8d809e",
    "question": "How are manifold control systems maintained to ensure they operate effectively?",
    "answer": "Regular cleaning and inspection"
  },
  {
    "number": 14,
    "questionId": "c784a886-eb27-4e3e-8ef5-e1f7899f83bb",
    "question": "Who must witness a 24-hour standing pressure test?",
    "answer": "An ASSE 6020 inspector, an ASSE 6030 verifier, or the Authority Having Jurisdiction(or a designee of)",
    "code_section": "5.1.12.2.6.7"
  },
  {
    "number": 15,
    "questionId": "b1c194f4-0d19-4639-8171-550263c47edd",
    "question": "Which valves should not be located in a room with station outlets or inlets that they control?",
    "answer": "zone",
    "code_section": "5.1.4.6.1"
  },
  {
    "number": 16,
    "questionId": "f2bb8f0b-aa6f-4e32-b7ac-2b0a297ed620",
    "question": "New or replacement valves are not required to be which type?",
    "answer": "ball type"
  },
  {
    "number": 17,
    "questionId": "41372e28-9532-43ec-8ce0-5644d2405b6e",
    "question": "Which alarm system acts as a primary alert mechanism for medical gas systems?",
    "answer": "Master alarm systems"
  },
  {
    "number": 18,
    "questionId": "85097844-054d-4a50-b911-90ef95751e1e",
    "question": "Which component is essential for preventing backflow in a multi-pump vacuum system?",
    "answer": "Check valve"
  },
  {
    "number": 20,
    "questionId": "a4b38e60-a9de-4ae9-9e90-be2d4a172e3d",
    "question": "How many seals must separate the oil-containing section from the compression chamber in reciprocating compressors for medical air?",
    "answer": "1",
    "code_section": "5.1.3.6.3.4"
  },
  {
    "number": 21,
    "questionId": "205e1828-2870-4ff2-9280-1705d03a2e18",
    "question": "The scale range of positive pressure analog indicators shall have the normal operating pressure fall within which part of the gauge scale?",
    "answer": "Middle third",
    "code_section": "5.1.8.1.3"
  },
  {
    "number": 22,
    "questionId": "3cc448ba-1494-444c-bd2a-c695edefd138",
    "question": "Where should area alarm pressure sensors be installed in anesthetizing gas delivery areas?",
    "answer": "Source or patient"
  },
  {
    "number": 23,
    "questionId": "43e7469f-bb85-4e02-bbe4-88a234afe4d3",
    "question": "Medical air sources shall only be used for which applications?",
    "answer": "Human respiratory applications",
    "code_section": "5.1.3.6.2"
  },
  {
    "number": 24,
    "questionId": "d6d9978d-4850-4014-91ff-6e7dfde25394",
    "question": "Station outlets that operate at a pressure in excess of what PSI shall be either D.I.S.S. or be designed to relieve pressure prior to removal of adapter?",
    "answer": "80",
    "code_section": "5.1.5.15"
  },
  {
    "number": 26,
    "questionId": "5de768ca-0b2e-4d81-b82c-55af008e4668",
    "question": "Underground piping buried outside of buildings shall have an installation procedure to what while being backfilled?",
    "answer": "Protect"
  },
  {
    "number": 27,
    "questionId": "8672e109-6fb9-4dd9-9d0b-442dfd8afae1",
    "question": "Regardless of how many zone valve boxes are installed on a lateral branch off a riser, only one what type of valve is required for each branch?",
    "answer": "service"
  },
  {
    "number": 28,
    "questionId": "89f5d654-de2e-4642-ab5d-2980700ab13c",
    "question": "Which ASTM standard is NOT applicable to medical-surgical vacuum system piping made from hard-drawn seamless copper tube?",
    "answer": "ASTM B597"
  },
  {
    "number": 29,
    "questionId": "f198f296-0a2d-49d6-84b3-7befa90db2b3",
    "question": "What is an incorrect assumption about medical gas pipeline systems?",
    "answer": "They can operate without relief valves"
  },
  {
    "number": 30,
    "questionId": "c8e128a9-f317-40f0-b9d7-a2ae3d5b1aaf",
    "question": "In a vacuum system, what occurs when not enough vacuum is maintained?",
    "answer": "Air entry"
  },
  {
    "number": 31,
    "questionId": "57e1d6fc-a714-4b68-95b9-c97479603d24",
    "question": "Which of the following NPS is allowed for connecting tubing for alarms?",
    "answer": "1/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 32,
    "questionId": "42490394-872c-4140-a142-04999e3a77bc",
    "question": "Where should the emergency oxygen supply connection be placed when multiple buildings are served from a single cryogenic liquid oxygen source?",
    "answer": "Each building served"
  },
  {
    "number": 33,
    "questionId": "81abfdaf-9284-425d-9692-402746a81f36",
    "question": "A medical-surgical vacuum receiver shall be made serviceable by which method?",
    "answer": "any method to ensure the continuation of service"
  },
  {
    "number": 34,
    "questionId": "41d7af66-3f5e-4290-b8a7-e8f2220e3a02",
    "question": "Mains and branches in medical gas piping systems shall be not less than which NPS?",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "number": 35,
    "questionId": "9ccc00e1-d27e-4308-af2d-bdc97e978e1a",
    "question": "Intake air for instrument air compressors shall not be drawn from which source?",
    "answer": "C) medical air intake"
  },
  {
    "number": 36,
    "questionId": "0c8acbaf-7ed0-4ec0-aca7-8a6ca6e82cd0",
    "question": "Which components are essential for the operation of central supply systems in a medical setting?",
    "answer": "Check valves and filters"
  },
  {
    "number": 37,
    "questionId": "87784ff7-1652-402e-b242-562cecc3b7c8",
    "question": "Cylinders in use must not exceed a temperature of which specified degree Fahrenheit?",
    "answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "number": 38,
    "questionId": "381947a1-f30f-485b-9564-c005cc6a11f7",
    "question": "Instrument air sources shall produce air at a gauge pressure of not less than how many PSIG?",
    "answer": "C) 200"
  },
  {
    "number": 39,
    "questionId": "ea21355e-0e2b-4fb5-9f46-04dfc3e6505c",
    "question": "Locations for central supply systems shall have what type of devices protected from physical damage?",
    "answer": "Electrical"
  },
  {
    "number": 40,
    "questionId": "ca8f715d-86c7-423d-8a91-0c53adecfcc8",
    "question": "How many connections should manifolds for gas cylinders have at a minimum?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "number": 41,
    "questionId": "bff9e90b-81bc-4e0b-aa69-48de9ac6460b",
    "question": "What is the purpose of performing a standing pressure test?",
    "answer": "Ensure system integrity"
  },
  {
    "number": 42,
    "questionId": "6b576d1d-4983-4d27-8226-d12abbfa7801",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a requirement for the quality of instrument air?",
    "answer": "A) dry to a dew point of 35*F"
  },
  {
    "number": 43,
    "questionId": "1a0118dc-63d8-432e-8680-fab0bb6c50c7",
    "question": "Inspection and testing shall be performed on all new piped gas systems to ensure all applicable provisions have been adhered to and system integrity has been achieved or maintained through a?",
    "answer": "documented procedure"
  },
  {
    "number": 44,
    "questionId": "17e18bd9-5c7e-44db-b87c-53ac90d284c1",
    "question": "Which type of emergency reserve system can be substituted for the EOSC?",
    "answer": "In-building"
  },
  {
    "number": 45,
    "questionId": "d69ed1ff-885e-4973-bd3c-e7c0bb3a3e64",
    "question": "What kind of indicators shall all master, area, and local alarm systems include for each condition monitored?",
    "answer": "Visual, audible"
  },
  {
    "number": 46,
    "questionId": "635300a2-42cf-4ef4-87e0-d20e6cc429c5",
    "question": "What type of connectors shall be used to connect the vacuum pumps with their intake and outlet piping?",
    "answer": "flexible"
  },
  {
    "number": 47,
    "questionId": "8281ad0e-35d4-42e5-958c-07cb0574695b",
    "question": "What are all brazed joints required to be examined for during the initial pressure test?",
    "answer": "leakage by means of a leak detectant safe for oxygen"
  },
  {
    "number": 48,
    "questionId": "c3169618-9d5f-4555-9a5e-049ccdc1147a",
    "question": "Performance qualification of brazers shall remain in effect indefinitely unless the brazer does not braze with the qualified procedure for a period exceeding how many months?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "number": 49,
    "questionId": "321d9061-ed97-4bc0-9e4c-17fa301dcce6",
    "question": "Final line filters for instrument air must be rated for a minimum of what efficiency at microns?",
    "answer": ".01"
  },
  {
    "number": 50,
    "questionId": "151e4aa8-2279-4bf8-a455-1baf54726c28",
    "question": "Where should medical air piping systems at different operating pressures separate?",
    "answer": "Filters"
  },
  {
    "number": 51,
    "questionId": "8584b907-6fd8-47c9-89ae-2267220a4646",
    "question": "Who shall conduct the verification testing?",
    "answer": "a party other than the installing contractor"
  },
  {
    "number": 52,
    "questionId": "6ddb9c7a-749d-4525-88ba-6f614ea5b723",
    "question": "What is the main purpose of having a pressure relief valve in a medical gas system?",
    "answer": "B) To prevent system overpressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 53,
    "questionId": "5fafa9bd-a854-4933-8571-453a338e8a42",
    "question": "When multiple vacuum pumps are joined to a common exhaust, the common exhaust must be sized to achieve what?",
    "answer": "Minimize back pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 54,
    "questionId": "9a5292c1-d53b-469d-a365-317b55d4846c",
    "question": "An automatic means in a medical air compressor system is required to prevent what?",
    "answer": "Backflow"
  },
  {
    "number": 55,
    "questionId": "f07fb948-e705-485b-85b4-e3644acb5aed",
    "question": "Which of the following systems shall not be permitted to be located in an outdoor enclosure?",
    "answer": "Medical air sources"
  },
  {
    "number": 56,
    "questionId": "f46d3113-7245-4928-8ee6-35ff57f6d203",
    "question": "What piping material is permitted for field-installed medical-surgical vacuum distribution systems?",
    "answer": "Stainless steel pipe"
  },
  {
    "number": 57,
    "questionId": "3ee31404-2656-43be-81ec-85fdfd36fa9b",
    "question": "Which standard is NOT a requirement for the quality of medical air?",
    "answer": "Be filtered to .01 microns"
  },
  {
    "number": 58,
    "questionId": "699675a1-834b-4b5b-b5a6-421c02810a83",
    "question": "For what parameter is a high water level sensor needed in air receivers?",
    "answer": "Avoiding system failure"
  },
  {
    "number": 59,
    "questionId": "d2e57363-6370-434e-9463-a99733d8e45d",
    "question": "Cylinders in use and in storage shall be prevented from reaching temperatures in excess of what degree Fahrenheit?",
    "answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "number": 60,
    "questionId": "acf505f9-670a-42e9-a91c-62fe5b0c56c3",
    "question": "Alarm switches and sensors must be installed to ensure they are what?",
    "answer": "Removable"
  },
  {
    "number": 61,
    "questionId": "5b4941ce-1535-42a7-ab08-3dacd444c3ce",
    "question": "A continuous tape or marker placed immediately above the buried pipe must clearly identify the pipeline by what?",
    "answer": "Specific name"
  },
  {
    "number": 62,
    "questionId": "aa12e698-8cdc-4f12-a613-f3c635bbb246",
    "question": "What feature should not be equipped on medical air receivers?",
    "answer": "A temperature indicator"
  },
  {
    "number": 63,
    "questionId": "c59c4758-a1c7-4ddd-b744-40a04dca2d14",
    "question": "Category 1 medical-surgical vacuum sources shall have an automatic means to prevent what from any on-cycle pump through and off-cycle pump?",
    "answer": "backflow"
  },
  {
    "number": 64,
    "questionId": "2351a571-74bc-4246-af33-8e73b2a121a4",
    "question": "In medical gas systems, the purpose of a pressure relief valve is to?",
    "answer": "discharge excess pressure safely"
  },
  {
    "number": 65,
    "questionId": "f851e26b-7d13-4f3e-9fe1-24bfbb7d41ce",
    "question": "At what CO level (in PPM) shall carbon monoxide activate the required alarms?",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "number": 66,
    "questionId": "2cc00a34-84b8-4450-b8b0-9f105d28774d",
    "question": "Medical air compressors that are oil-based require what type of filter?",
    "answer": "Coalescing filters"
  },
  {
    "number": 67,
    "questionId": "7254f9dc-e922-4042-b1df-4c373502ce37",
    "question": "What is the minimum clearance around EOSC for a temporary source of supply?",
    "answer": "3 ft"
  },
  {
    "number": 68,
    "questionId": "75cacf2e-8cc2-42f9-935b-baf6113361b7",
    "question": "Liquids drained from a category 3 vacuum source shall discharge _ to a sanitary drainage system?",
    "answer": "indirectly"
  },
  {
    "number": 69,
    "questionId": "d8d87af7-141a-4936-b68f-41652911e1bd",
    "question": "What is the required relief setting for valves in central supply systems for positive pressure gases above normal working operating pressure?",
    "answer": "50%"
  },
  {
    "number": 70,
    "questionId": "720e86f5-34de-41e9-9188-8f3d23a85833",
    "question": "When is the initial pressure test conducted by the installer?",
    "answer": "after blow down of the distribution piping"
  },
  {
    "number": 71,
    "questionId": "07063fc8-f3da-4ebb-bce0-e6932632d7a5",
    "question": "When the dew point at system pressure exceeds what temperature in Fahrenheit, an alarm is activated?",
    "answer": "-22"
  },
  {
    "number": 72,
    "questionId": "592a0aaa-cd10-4e97-985e-fe74cc9d9ce5",
    "question": "What is the consequence if a brazer does not perform brazing for a duration exceeding 6 months?",
    "answer": "Qualifying period resets"
  },
  {
    "number": 73,
    "questionId": "61012c73-05cc-4340-97ab-c760e2dada7e",
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of an alarm in a medical-surgical vacuum system?",
    "answer": "To notify failures in the vacuum system"
  },
  {
    "number": 74,
    "questionId": "d8941f59-b1ad-4974-85b0-cb30dac334bd",
    "question": "Where should the master alarm panel be located for the individual responsible for the maintenance of the medical gas piping system?",
    "answer": "Office or work space of the individual"
  },
  {
    "number": 75,
    "questionId": "4c28d726-daa0-4289-8741-ab0bbaf48c02",
    "question": "The initial pressure test requires leakage detection that does not contain which of the following?",
    "answer": "ammonia"
  },
  {
    "number": 76,
    "questionId": "d8aeb6d5-9ab7-4a1d-a860-944ff171f333",
    "question": "Each station outlet/inlet for medical gases and vacuums shall be what type?",
    "answer": "gas-specific"
  },
  {
    "number": 77,
    "questionId": "f9e1e1b6-96c6-4836-bd8e-c9b9310b7715",
    "question": "Which location is medical gas piping allowed to be installed in?",
    "answer": "Patient care areas"
  },
  {
    "number": 78,
    "questionId": "8db4c9a8-0e47-4915-be70-7da670e3b17b",
    "question": "Which of the following filler metals shall be used to braze copper-to-copper joints in medical gas and vacuum distribution piping?",
    "answer": "BCuP series"
  },
  {
    "number": 79,
    "questionId": "e1abcb93-79e5-42a5-9f38-2fdf403ab8dd",
    "question": "Vacuum receivers should be capable of withstanding a gauge of how many inches of HgV?",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "number": 80,
    "questionId": "36945be4-d24c-4263-a969-f3329f5ba60d",
    "question": "A system shall be deemed breached as a result of all of the following except?",
    "answer": "alarm testing"
  },
  {
    "number": 81,
    "questionId": "e555d569-f403-4c13-b14c-5fdf60cdc55f",
    "question": "The quality of instrument air shall be dry to a dew point of what temperature?",
    "answer": "A) -40*F"
  },
  {
    "number": 82,
    "questionId": "929b48d7-21f9-4aff-844e-1ebbe394f4cd",
    "question": "What type of indicator is required for final line filters for instrument air to show the status of filter life?",
    "answer": "visual"
  },
  {
    "number": 83,
    "questionId": "e0c5e4f6-0dd2-4ac9-8681-5c4f53b26252",
    "question": "Medical air filters must be sized for what percentage of the system peak calculated demand?",
    "answer": "100%"
  },
  {
    "number": 84,
    "questionId": "7837acc4-9022-45ae-b002-6a55cda1b269",
    "question": "What treatment is required for water used in liquid ring compressors to prevent pathogens and chlorine?",
    "answer": "Hypochlorination"
  },
  {
    "number": 85,
    "questionId": "b6d0c262-4d1c-49f5-a6e7-ccac34a976d2",
    "question": "Which type of gas shall not be used to power the venture of a WAGD system?",
    "answer": "Medical air"
  },
  {
    "number": 86,
    "questionId": "547c66d3-b607-4ddf-9c07-09d0fe109c91",
    "question": "What minimum efficiency rating is required for medical air filters at 1 micron or greater?",
    "answer": "98%"
  },
  {
    "number": 87,
    "questionId": "517a88cc-671b-4d24-872a-3136848a960b",
    "question": "A Category 1 dedicated WAGD source must consist of how many producers to serve the peak calculated demand?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "number": 88,
    "questionId": "f30158e5-288b-4961-a02b-a598f601426f",
    "question": "Brazing procedures and brazer performance for the installation of medical gas and vacuum piping shall be qualified in accordance with?",
    "answer": "ASME section IX or AWS B2.2"
  },
  {
    "number": 89,
    "questionId": "9cece3e3-6f50-4e85-b06a-f6a4449e4cb3",
    "question": "What dew point temperature activates the instrument air dew point high alarm?",
    "answer": "-22°F"
  },
  {
    "number": 90,
    "questionId": "8b3a88fb-e96e-42c5-ab74-5d10f0a301c6",
    "question": "What is installed in each header of central supply systems to prevent debris from entering the manifold controls?",
    "answer": "Filter"
  },
  {
    "number": 91,
    "questionId": "46f5dd0f-3d1c-4980-9273-3203213668de",
    "question": "The minimum backfilled cover above the top of the pipe or its enclosure shall be 36 inches, except that the minimum cover shall be permitted to be reduced to how many inches where there is no potential damage from surface loads or surface conditions?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "number": 92,
    "questionId": "3c66a1ec-31dc-40c7-aea1-e463e6da210c",
    "question": "What is the maximum allowable pressure for a vacuum source in dental systems?",
    "answer": "25 psi"
  },
  {
    "number": 93,
    "questionId": "66064e67-81d1-4505-9c83-c742f84435b6",
    "question": "Verification testing for medical gas and vacuum pipeline systems must meet the requirements of which standard?",
    "answer": "ASSE standard 6030"
  },
  {
    "number": 94,
    "questionId": "68504129-3a3f-4b4e-b601-f6b4ce170e3f",
    "question": "The initial pressure test for positive pressure gases and vacuum systems shall have a test pressure of 1.5 times the system working pressure, but not less than what PSI?",
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "number": 95,
    "questionId": "41753799-9ec2-4ae0-89cc-cd044b1c7146",
    "question": "A medical-surgical vacuum system should always aim to minimize what?",
    "answer": "Back pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 96,
    "questionId": "b9d32a65-3938-4608-a8a3-505664f05d7f",
    "question": "The responsible authority shall review the inspection and testing records prior to the use of all systems to ensure that all findings have been successfully completed. Who is this authority?",
    "answer": "responsible facility authority"
  },
  {
    "number": 97,
    "questionId": "71e6ea2c-f631-4011-9be2-0cdd015531bc",
    "question": "What is the scale range of vacuum indicators measured in inches of HgV?",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "number": 98,
    "questionId": "d48d43f9-a524-4493-8afd-65735a7967cd",
    "question": "Which component is not part of an auxiliary source connection?",
    "answer": "Visual pressure indicator"
  },
  {
    "number": 99,
    "questionId": "500cc72b-cfc0-49a2-b17c-88613c3c0b0e",
    "question": "Station outlets and inlets of manufactured assemblies that employ hose or flexible connections to the piping system that are not fully and immediately accessible shall use what type of connectors?",
    "answer": "D.I.S.S."
  },
  {
    "number": 100,
    "questionId": "c7e31f84-1790-4e68-924e-71259035a2b5",
    "question": "What does a signal from each local alarm system indicate at the master alarm panels?",
    "answer": "Source equipment issue is present"
  },
  {
    "number": 101,
    "questionId": "c54deb1d-ba76-419f-96f8-525385a4384e",
    "question": "In positive pressure systems, area alarm sensors for critical care areas must be located on which side of the zone valve box assemblies?",
    "answer": "Patient or use side"
  },
  {
    "number": 102,
    "questionId": "28baada5-1a31-4953-bd26-804b7419ad3d",
    "question": "A standard gauge pressure of 160-185 psi applies to which of the following?",
    "answer": "instrument air"
  },
  {
    "number": 103,
    "questionId": "8cf65923-06c4-4942-9c83-8d7e93f595d5",
    "question": "Runouts to alarm panels and connecting tubing for gauges and alarm devices shall be permitted to be which NPS?",
    "answer": "1/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 104,
    "questionId": "e1fcc402-a5fe-4f1a-a3e9-209a1a345d82",
    "question": "The manufacturer is allowed a decay of less than what percentage in 24 hours during the standing pressure test?",
    "answer": "1.0"
  },
  {
    "number": 105,
    "questionId": "900fb9e6-3495-47f4-a642-94b234b86489",
    "question": "Which of the following is critical for the safe operation of medical gas systems regarding pressure levels?",
    "answer": "Monitoring at the source"
  },
  {
    "number": 106,
    "questionId": "e3bf403e-7ded-49c2-9e7d-b11331423b39",
    "question": "What is the maximum permitted interval for spacing pipe labels?",
    "answer": "20 feet"
  },
  {
    "number": 107,
    "questionId": "347458be-1511-4aea-a090-1c4780ad7235",
    "question": "Who is responsible for ensuring that fittings for positive pressure medical gas systems are cleaned for oxygen service before installation?",
    "answer": "Manufacturer"
  },
  {
    "number": 108,
    "questionId": "980ae343-940a-4488-96bd-270478fb6567",
    "question": "Factory installed outlet tubing on station inlets shall not be less than what NPS?",
    "answer": "3/8"
  },
  {
    "number": 109,
    "questionId": "9a9fd8ae-2496-4fc2-b846-a3fdd94628f9",
    "question": "When should the dew point monitor activate alarms in the medical air system?",
    "answer": "When dew point exceeds 35°F"
  },
  {
    "number": 110,
    "questionId": "22807c58-2d60-4508-b6d4-4d6e493c8c94",
    "question": "Why is it important for the master alarm panel to be monitored continuously?",
    "answer": "To ensure rapid response to any issues"
  },
  {
    "number": 111,
    "questionId": "8a77e78a-7f79-45bb-aa76-fa257c803d98",
    "question": "Immediately outside of each vital life-support, critical care, and anesthetizing location, there shall be what type of valve for each medical gas, vacuum, and WAGD system?",
    "answer": "zone"
  },
  {
    "number": 112,
    "questionId": "70b09fee-5130-4e97-abe6-2f15484680e3",
    "question": "Which valve is typically used to control the flow of medical gases in a treatment facility?",
    "answer": "shutoff valve"
  },
  {
    "number": 113,
    "questionId": "e184268a-ebe7-47b6-86b2-0fc0661d2926",
    "question": "Which of the following does NOT represent an indicator in the alarm system?",
    "answer": "Mock signal"
  },
  {
    "number": 114,
    "questionId": "ff1b2396-1d87-4827-99da-608bd70b7ac2",
    "question": "Supports in damp locations must be?",
    "answer": "Plastic-coated"
  },
  {
    "number": 115,
    "questionId": "0c0a273c-90c8-4f6f-b75c-8a03d0708d23",
    "question": "At what percentage from normal operating pressure will the master alarm system activate?",
    "answer": "20%"
  },
  {
    "number": 116,
    "questionId": "c8562121-3af7-46d0-bc0b-b4224acfd68f",
    "question": "Which document defines the qualifications for installers of medical gas systems?",
    "answer": "ASSE standard 6010"
  },
  {
    "number": 117,
    "questionId": "676bcd6f-d5a9-441e-b6bc-ca0aba928afa",
    "question": "What type of material is recommended for the piping of category 3 medical gases?",
    "answer": "seamless copper"
  },
  {
    "number": 118,
    "questionId": "9768df2b-de27-4832-932a-1a51ee3cf25b",
    "question": "Who must furnish documentation certifying that all installed piping and materials are cleaned for oxygen service?",
    "answer": "Installer"
  },
  {
    "number": 119,
    "questionId": "1bf5ad9f-22fe-446b-88eb-57ec25ef390a",
    "question": "Mains and branches in medical-surgical vacuum systems shall not be less than which NPS?",
    "answer": "3/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 120,
    "questionId": "d7c587a3-fa75-49e1-84d2-901d3809167a",
    "question": "What qualification is required to install a category 2 medical gas system?",
    "answer": "ASSE 6010"
  },
  {
    "number": 121,
    "questionId": "d4a668f8-6794-4136-a77e-b04a098973f5",
    "question": "What is a function of the final line regulator in a medical air system?",
    "answer": "Monitors the pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 122,
    "questionId": "9411e0b2-fca4-4cc7-839b-492dbe94a6c2",
    "question": "What is the initial pressure test pressure for a category 2 system?",
    "answer": "1.5 but not less than 150 psi"
  },
  {
    "number": 123,
    "questionId": "8850a6b1-1e15-4982-8a8b-86f1938799eb",
    "question": "WAGD producers designed for operation at vacuums below how many inches of HgV shall only be used for WAGD service?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "number": 124,
    "questionId": "7955ae0c-2963-4653-943a-bdb2707a5fb1",
    "question": "What minimum distance is prescribed for medical air intakes from exhausts to avoid contamination?",
    "answer": "25 ft"
  },
  {
    "number": 125,
    "questionId": "386165b4-2738-4b2f-9187-35561e9fd2b4",
    "question": "Pressure relief valves for dental air systems having less than _ ft3 at STP shall be permitted to discharge locally indoors?",
    "answer": "3000"
  },
  {
    "number": 126,
    "questionId": "e3dd60bd-c1d2-4546-a6c2-c400471e7796",
    "question": "All positive pressure supply systems shall be provided with duplex line pressure regulators piped in which configuration?",
    "answer": "Parallel"
  },
  {
    "number": 127,
    "questionId": "646da960-4f72-4d14-9be5-13a45460ec68",
    "question": "The labeling shall be what for all components of the system?",
    "answer": "D) verified"
  },
  {
    "number": 128,
    "questionId": "55cdfad1-7021-4439-8b44-5a2f9c95da21",
    "question": "Instrument air sources shall be filtered with what type of filters located upstream of the final line regulators?",
    "answer": "A) activated carbon"
  },
  {
    "number": 129,
    "questionId": "45111e66-e42d-4b89-9f29-6737938506ce",
    "question": "How often should medical gas systems undergo testing for compliance and safety?",
    "answer": "A) Annually"
  },
  {
    "number": 130,
    "questionId": "21b115b9-117e-477b-9612-45c4ad06b3d3",
    "question": "What should a medical air compressor system's pressure relief valve be set at above line pressure?",
    "answer": "50 percent"
  },
  {
    "number": 131,
    "questionId": "bdbd46fe-ac25-433f-b78b-4c51a4f88893",
    "question": "To assure that all ambient air has been removed from the pipeline prior to brazing, what shall be used to verify the effectiveness of the purge?",
    "answer": "oxygen analyzer"
  },
  {
    "number": 132,
    "questionId": "01e33b41-9bb3-44ee-a1cd-6e8adf94e8dd",
    "question": "What type of signal is required to indicate the operating status of manifolds for gas cylinders?",
    "answer": "Local"
  },
  {
    "number": 133,
    "questionId": "0d1a6ce0-1b36-4fa4-aba2-ddeefd404caf",
    "question": "Area alarms shall be tested to verify an alarm condition if the pressure in the piping system increases or decreases by what percentage?",
    "answer": "B) 20"
  },
  {
    "number": 134,
    "questionId": "a931c685-caee-4368-a223-6b2c739de81d",
    "question": "What is the minimum height requirement for the medical air intake above ground level?",
    "answer": "20 ft"
  },
  {
    "number": 135,
    "questionId": "0cc7e804-ce5b-4202-a869-672c862b1986",
    "question": "What percentage indicates a pressure increase or decrease for area alarm panels in medical gas systems from normal operating pressure?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "number": 136,
    "questionId": "f0eafad8-d237-439e-9b31-43aed4bc4129",
    "question": "What is the test gas used by the installer?",
    "answer": "Nitrogen NF"
  },
  {
    "number": 137,
    "questionId": "6bbca101-49a1-43e1-912e-b269b8095bd3",
    "question": "While brazing medical-gas copper joints, a purge gas shall flow continuously to prevent the formation of copper oxide on the inside surface of the joint. What shall be used as a purge gas?",
    "answer": "nitrogen NF"
  },
  {
    "number": 138,
    "questionId": "3b2ad379-2250-4cfc-8caa-6e6db409a246",
    "question": "Drops to individual station outlets and inlets shall not be less than which NPS?",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "number": 139,
    "questionId": "d329a152-43b3-4d80-bcbf-eb0772b93373",
    "question": "WAGD can be produced by all of the following except which source?",
    "answer": "Medical air source"
  },
  {
    "number": 140,
    "questionId": "511067b8-700e-461b-a1b1-2bd83c5b4ca5",
    "question": "Which valves allow modification of lateral branch piping from a main or riser without shutting down the entire main, riser, or facility?",
    "answer": "service"
  },
  {
    "number": 141,
    "questionId": "2ad5be84-31ff-4803-a9f4-fa09a2d11a91",
    "question": "What type of alarm panel is permitted for category 2 warning systems?",
    "answer": "single"
  },
  {
    "number": 142,
    "questionId": "d04020bb-4bd4-4f11-b08f-7336bc819ba1",
    "question": "What should be monitored to ensure safe operation of medical air systems?",
    "answer": "Pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 143,
    "questionId": "38c34004-8752-4919-a18b-df5f677381a1",
    "question": "The initial pressure test for positive pressure gases ensures that the system is tested to prevent what kind of issue?",
    "answer": "leakage"
  },
  {
    "number": 144,
    "questionId": "880d341a-9fa1-409c-9daf-543faba1a895",
    "question": "For brazed joints, which temperature in degrees Fahrenheit must the melting temperature of the brazing alloy exceed to maintain piping integrity in a fire?",
    "answer": "1000"
  },
  {
    "number": 145,
    "questionId": "5d678db6-b5dc-4347-a794-bf4ca5299480",
    "question": "In what category is the loss of the piped gas and vacuum systems not likely to cause injury to patients, staff, or visitors, but can cause discomfort?",
    "answer": "category 3"
  },
  {
    "number": 146,
    "questionId": "f18bec4b-9fd2-4fd1-892e-96d1425d80f2",
    "question": "When determining no cross connection exists between various systems, one system is charged with nitrogen NF at what PSI?",
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "number": 147,
    "questionId": "751105ed-7482-4965-95d2-e0f511ae6627",
    "question": "Medical air reconstituted from oxygen USP and nitrogen NF should meet all of the following requirements except?",
    "answer": "completion of a risk analysis and approval by authority having jurisdiction before use"
  },
  {
    "number": 148,
    "questionId": "7c837d4c-fbaa-438f-b745-e20253d9bd48",
    "question": "When using the autogenous orbital welding process, joints shall be continuously what inside and outside with inert gas as qualified with a procedure?",
    "answer": "purged"
  },
  {
    "number": 149,
    "questionId": "7c568f95-a485-4592-b9b4-50c60facfd2c",
    "question": "Pipe labels shall be located at intervals of not more than how many feet?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "number": 150,
    "questionId": "f0a992b7-8c40-4afb-aee8-3ec7f4e8148c",
    "question": "If another alarm condition occurs while the audible alarm is silenced, what must happen?",
    "answer": "The audible signal shall re-initiate"
  },
  {
    "number": 151,
    "questionId": "5ece5f46-322f-403f-8634-a741857c5bd3",
    "question": "What pressure drop in the medical-surgical vacuum system triggers the master alarm system?",
    "answer": "Any value below 12 in. HgV"
  },
  {
    "number": 152,
    "questionId": "a90745b2-5b89-48ca-9615-9c976fb530e9",
    "question": "The standing pressure test for positive pressure medical gas piping shall be conducted with the source valve closed at a test pressure of what percentage above normal system operating pressure for 24 hours?",
    "answer": "20% above normal system operating pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 153,
    "questionId": "f04dcf01-dec2-453f-8294-b04a6a1ee86e",
    "question": "On system renovation where no piping is changed, what type of testing shall be performed to ensure no other equipment in the system has been adversely impacted?",
    "answer": "functional"
  },
  {
    "number": 154,
    "questionId": "c2370859-876f-4cf2-8afe-5509888d1085",
    "question": "What purpose do alarm systems serve in medical gas installations?",
    "answer": "Monitor conditions"
  },
  {
    "number": 155,
    "questionId": "015c2a66-7d69-422f-82fe-9b7a9bfeba1e",
    "question": "During a vacuum piping system test, a test pressure of 12 inches HgV is applied for how long?",
    "answer": "24 hours"
  },
  {
    "number": 156,
    "questionId": "732d61ac-02a2-4898-ac78-0078542f22ea",
    "question": "What should aftercoolers be provided with?",
    "answer": "Flexible connectors"
  },
  {
    "number": 157,
    "questionId": "22cf1344-c64f-47e8-9c6a-784fbd8f261c",
    "question": "Who must ensure that inspection and testing adhere to applicable provisions?",
    "answer": "documented procedure"
  },
  {
    "number": 158,
    "questionId": "fd1a5eb6-5029-4d8c-84d7-2da700d9e32f",
    "question": "Which type of compressor can introduce oil into the medical air system if not configured correctly?",
    "answer": "Reciprocating compressors"
  },
  {
    "number": 159,
    "questionId": "2025a9a3-03c4-4dba-9505-b45580e7cc0d",
    "question": "All pressure relief valves shall be made of brass, bronze, or which other material?",
    "answer": "Stainless steel"
  },
  {
    "number": 160,
    "questionId": "fbe0070e-69a6-4682-b21f-defd98ac828b",
    "question": "Outdoor locations surrounded by impermeable walls, except fire barrier walls, shall have protected ventilation openings at what part of each wall?",
    "answer": "Base"
  },
  {
    "number": 161,
    "questionId": "1177150a-a3ff-4fcc-9899-6947743d4d71",
    "question": "Vacuum piping systems shall be subjected to a 24-hour standing test at a pressure between what measurement of HgV and full vacuum?",
    "answer": "12 in"
  },
  {
    "number": 162,
    "questionId": "24262dde-0d9a-495c-956c-3d65700a1293",
    "question": "What is the acceptable accuracy range of digital indicators as a percentage of the operating pressure?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "number": 163,
    "questionId": "b224d669-0ea5-4886-b1e9-eaa561b0e59c",
    "question": "A low-pressure, vacuum insulated vessel containing gas in liquid form is called?",
    "answer": "container"
  },
  {
    "number": 164,
    "questionId": "fc970ed7-5b34-4288-bb98-8831de2b0002",
    "question": "A category 3 moisture indicator shall indicate when the relative humidity of the dental air exceeds _ at line pressure and temperature?",
    "answer": "40%"
  },
  {
    "number": 165,
    "questionId": "2ea1a438-5428-4a03-bdc6-149c1326d750",
    "question": "Threaded joints shall be allowed on the source equipment on which side of the source valve?",
    "answer": "source"
  },
  {
    "number": 166,
    "questionId": "cdba8f03-a1da-4424-8a6c-e337a9990273",
    "question": "Operational shutoff valves are permitted to be installed to isolate or shut off piping for servicing of what?",
    "answer": "in-line"
  },
  {
    "number": 167,
    "questionId": "7298d7bc-ac12-4d74-90bd-575c5550a37d",
    "question": "Gas-specific demand check fittings are not required on which type of indicators?",
    "answer": "Zone valve pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 168,
    "questionId": "9d203a07-c585-4f9c-8345-d54bba059707",
    "question": "Which aspect is crucial for maintaining safety during medical gas installations?",
    "answer": "C) Proper venting mechanisms"
  },
  {
    "number": 169,
    "questionId": "d6f48cef-fd12-474f-a4e5-64b6bf4b8a1a",
    "question": "Where category 3 medical gas supply systems supply two treatment facilities, each facility shall be provided with an emergency _ valve?",
    "answer": "shutoff"
  },
  {
    "number": 170,
    "questionId": "58432740-796f-444d-a6d2-47a6a828f6fa",
    "question": "Axially swaged fittings that provide a metal to metal seal having pressure and temperature ratings of a brazed joint when complete are?",
    "answer": "permanent"
  },
  {
    "number": 171,
    "questionId": "175a148e-efa2-4732-8b27-b81edd56319a",
    "question": "Flexible connectors, metallic or non-metallic, shall have a minimum burst pressure of how many PSI?",
    "answer": "1000"
  },
  {
    "number": 172,
    "questionId": "35280c97-3ce1-4ef1-b1c2-b84e473d23b7",
    "question": "In a vacuum exhaust system, which of the following cannot be used to isolate the pumps?",
    "answer": "Grooved joint"
  },
  {
    "number": 173,
    "questionId": "04f6ba84-ecd1-40a6-bec8-25f4982584be",
    "question": "Category 2 medical-surgical vacuum systems are permitted to be what configuration?",
    "answer": "simplex"
  },
  {
    "number": 174,
    "questionId": "c4908317-5d02-4534-ad91-23604582a020",
    "question": "Which type of oxygen system location is generally prohibited from having access to open flame areas?",
    "answer": "Indoor"
  },
  {
    "number": 175,
    "questionId": "9c9ff3ad-912b-4988-b984-1017434fd1d6",
    "question": "What type of alarm activates to indicate the operation of the backup compressor in an instrument air source?",
    "answer": "local"
  },
  {
    "number": 176,
    "questionId": "59e85105-f37d-4cfe-80ac-05b72fc33fcd",
    "question": "In a medical air supply system, what is required for dryers, filters, and regulators?",
    "answer": "At least duplexed"
  },
  {
    "number": 177,
    "questionId": "b937cfc9-8f30-430c-96e1-ffe2a6c4d18d",
    "question": "Cylinder and cryogenic liquid container outlet connections shall be designed as to render the attachment point unusable when removal of the outlet connection is attempted. What is the intended design outcome?",
    "answer": "Unusable"
  },
  {
    "number": 178,
    "questionId": "af92fe83-e055-49aa-b080-4b79bab0b687",
    "question": "Which type of gas is not allowed to be stored outdoors according to safety regulations?",
    "answer": "Medical air"
  },
  {
    "number": 179,
    "questionId": "badb5f2b-222e-455b-b69a-74531b19e854",
    "question": "Medical air receivers must allow for what during service?",
    "answer": "Being filled"
  },
  {
    "number": 180,
    "questionId": "1134fd8d-301f-498f-917c-68cba38c7b33",
    "question": "What type of alarm condition does the system provide an indication for?",
    "answer": "Pressure regulation"
  },
  {
    "number": 181,
    "questionId": "1189f2d7-59b8-45fc-81ab-5ab371d70011",
    "question": "A shutoff valve shall be placed at the immediate connection of each source system to what type of system?",
    "answer": "source"
  },
  {
    "number": 182,
    "questionId": "c69c301d-9eac-41f5-92aa-059781b3b6dc",
    "question": "Who is responsible for developing an emergency plan for medical air loss in a category 2 facility?",
    "answer": "facility staff"
  },
  {
    "number": 183,
    "questionId": "e500646a-5abf-41e4-95b5-9350a39278ff",
    "question": "Nitrous oxide and carbon dioxide using cylinders or portable containers shall be prevented from reaching temperatures lower than what degree Fahrenheit?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "number": 184,
    "questionId": "a230d8a1-4d0e-4809-b27a-83ac3b30d966",
    "question": "What is a necessary feature of medical air compressor systems regarding airflow?",
    "answer": "Backflow preventer"
  },
  {
    "number": 185,
    "questionId": "34d545e9-81d4-465d-8bec-96b415c47a5a",
    "question": "What is the minimum NPS for mains and branches in a medical gas piping system?",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "number": 186,
    "questionId": "3472af35-7836-4bd6-a74e-fe0578c4f94c",
    "question": "What type of alarm(s) shall activate when the backup or lag compressor is running?",
    "answer": "Local"
  },
  {
    "number": 187,
    "questionId": "539044f0-89c4-4b9c-9de8-86029508124e",
    "question": "What type of alarm does a Category 1 medical-surgical vacuum system activate when the backup pump is running?",
    "answer": "Local"
  },
  {
    "number": 188,
    "questionId": "43525e1a-636f-4318-848b-d5e8de9da742",
    "question": "What type of indicator is required for coalescing filters in oil-employing medical air compressors?",
    "answer": "An element change"
  },
  {
    "number": 189,
    "questionId": "2372f5bf-8002-4c10-8002-e43fd1dad504",
    "question": "In potentially damp locations, hangers or supports that are in contact with the tube shall be what or otherwise electrically insulated from the tube?",
    "answer": "Plastic-coated"
  },
  {
    "number": 190,
    "questionId": "a48d1a3e-fa70-4dcc-a5d0-2321601d7556",
    "question": "Where should medical air filters be located?",
    "answer": "Final line regulator"
  },
  {
    "number": 191,
    "questionId": "2cd72efc-8fa3-4553-8bfe-436f9f76eb98",
    "question": "In-line check valves are not required to have what feature?",
    "answer": "threaded end connections"
  },
  {
    "number": 192,
    "questionId": "8d8342b1-caa2-433d-9608-4915fa8150c7",
    "question": "Metallic flexible joints shall not be permitted in the pipeline for?",
    "answer": "dielectric breaks"
  },
  {
    "number": 193,
    "questionId": "988297bb-e276-4210-8640-a33ce0f8e99d",
    "question": "What is the minimum distance for the medical air intake from all doors, windows, or other openings in a building?",
    "answer": "10 ft"
  },
  {
    "number": 194,
    "questionId": "a74ccb87-761f-4ddc-b012-e302bf1245f5",
    "question": "Who shall provide documentation certifying the performance and successful completion of all pressure testing for a manufactured assembly?",
    "answer": "manufacturer"
  },
  {
    "number": 195,
    "questionId": "939f6c70-d3de-450b-8abb-014097917ec8",
    "question": "Which method is crucial for ensuring each pump can function independently in a common exhaust system?",
    "answer": "Check valve"
  },
  {
    "number": 196,
    "questionId": "7142f5c0-c92c-4069-a07e-0ac527e06eb5",
    "question": "The removal of components within a source system for repair and reinstallation shall be treated as new work for testing whenever work involves?",
    "answer": "cutting and brazing"
  },
  {
    "number": 197,
    "questionId": "9a5b464c-9a5f-483a-9751-18ade98b09cc",
    "question": "At what dew point temperature does the medical air dew point high alarm activate?",
    "answer": "+35°F"
  },
  {
    "number": 198,
    "questionId": "40754b13-0f91-41ed-927b-0032a75d4fdb",
    "question": "What type of alarm system triggers when a manifold bulk system is being utilized?",
    "answer": "Master alarm system"
  },
  {
    "number": 199,
    "questionId": "3f968d74-aa51-458e-81e7-3b5467a16a7d",
    "question": "Threaded joints in medical gas and medical-surgical vacuum systems shall be permitted for all of the following except?",
    "answer": "check valves in the main line"
  },
  {
    "number": 200,
    "questionId": "7abc2587-901b-4bf3-9426-b07be5639e18",
    "question": "Indoor locations for oxygen, nitrous oxide, and mixtures of these gases shall not communicate with any of the following except which?",
    "answer": "Designated storage area"
  },
  {
    "number": 201,
    "questionId": "90e77afe-2065-409a-b41e-4985f4efae78",
    "question": "Nitrogen and instrument air supply systems are considered what type of gasses?",
    "answer": "C) support"
  },
  {
    "number": 202,
    "questionId": "b4638763-e7bb-4d4e-8970-cff1992b334a",
    "question": "What type of valves shall be readily operable from a standing position in the corridor on the same floor they serve?",
    "answer": "zone"
  },
  {
    "number": 203,
    "questionId": "27b181fc-c5ae-47ce-9d8e-d5e518f5a7ac",
    "question": "Additional WAGD producers shall activate how when the operating producer fails to maintain required vacuum?",
    "answer": "Automatically"
  },
  {
    "number": 204,
    "questionId": "8af7fcca-4199-493b-a4ad-f01be40befd0",
    "question": "In patient care areas, medical gas piping must comply with which of the following requirements?",
    "answer": "Avoid open flame areas"
  },
  {
    "number": 205,
    "questionId": "4eb95a58-42f5-4fda-b67e-777a9413f5a7",
    "question": "Piping between the vacuum pump and the source shutoff valve shall not be made of which material?",
    "answer": "plastic (PVC)"
  },
  {
    "number": 206,
    "questionId": "cc54b8dd-86ba-430d-86bf-27b99d07d507",
    "question": "What type of audible indication should all medical gas alarm systems have for each condition monitored?",
    "answer": "Cancelable"
  },
  {
    "number": 207,
    "questionId": "35b3b261-047e-41f5-a4cf-47b09ab767a4",
    "question": "What is the primary function of a manifold in central supply systems?",
    "answer": "To provide a switching mechanism between gas sources"
  },
  {
    "number": 208,
    "questionId": "a8fae596-676b-4ccb-8b33-63d660ac1c3b",
    "question": "Which joining method is acceptable on category 1 medical gas and medical-surgical vacuum distribution pipeline systems?",
    "answer": "axially swaged fittings"
  },
  {
    "number": 209,
    "questionId": "612b9fff-e650-4408-ae45-236007e5a3b1",
    "question": "Where should the pressure in the main line of each medical gas system, and the operation and condition of the source of supply, be monitored?",
    "answer": "Master alarm"
  },
  {
    "number": 210,
    "questionId": "a5fa5ec4-aa9d-47dd-a23c-2d0c8bc95aaf",
    "question": "When a medical-surgical vacuum source is incapable of maintaining the required vacuum, additional pumps shall be activated how?",
    "answer": "automatically"
  },
  {
    "number": 211,
    "questionId": "fdccbfeb-e015-45fc-8bfd-5d85f5883bc1",
    "question": "What should be included in the auxiliary source connection for a medical gas system?",
    "answer": "Valves"
  },
  {
    "number": 212,
    "questionId": "54b0c4d1-4e32-427a-8751-1fb864548914",
    "question": "What type of shutoff valve shall be provided in the main supply line when the source valve is inaccessible from within the building?",
    "answer": "main"
  },
  {
    "number": 213,
    "questionId": "603ab9f5-7641-4b9a-b314-042b547ae00c",
    "question": "Nfpa 99 requires tubing to be cut using a sharp tubing cutter that shall be free from grease, oil, and other lubricants not suitable for oxygen service. After cutting, tubing ends shall be permitted to be?",
    "answer": "rolled smooth or deburred"
  },
  {
    "number": 214,
    "questionId": "d72e1626-7ee1-4c4b-983a-530e0a29eadf",
    "question": "What can substitute one of the alarm panels in a master alarm system?",
    "answer": "Centralized computer system"
  },
  {
    "number": 215,
    "questionId": "2afa8521-7dc4-4a91-9796-ad1adc59979d",
    "question": "An existing system that is not in strict compliance with the provisions of the code shall be permitted to be continued in use as long as the authority having jurisdiction has determined that such use does not constitute a distinct hazard to life. Who is this authority?",
    "answer": "Authority having jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    "number": 216,
    "questionId": "80bcc0f9-5c76-4980-864d-120256495831",
    "question": "At what parts per million (ppm) do local alarms activate for high carbon monoxide levels in a medical air system?",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "number": 217,
    "questionId": "e222fe84-aa21-40ec-bf4f-9b6e4840a1a4",
    "question": "What percentage of the zones shall be tested at the outlet most remote from the source by the verifier to complete the piping particulate test?",
    "answer": "A) 25"
  },
  {
    "number": 218,
    "questionId": "b5f0f2ab-5aa5-4df4-b60b-c016ba12389a",
    "question": "How many master alarm panels can a single initiating device actuate?",
    "answer": "Multiple master alarm panels"
  },
  {
    "number": 219,
    "questionId": "4434539b-6738-4295-b970-4430423c4eab",
    "question": "What type of sensor should be equipped in air receivers that use liquid ring compressors or water-cooled aftercoolers?",
    "answer": "High water level"
  },
  {
    "number": 220,
    "questionId": "a5ee52bd-215f-4c72-aa8b-1d7dcdd8638f",
    "question": "To facilitate service, testing, or replacement, what should be provided downstream of the source valve?",
    "answer": "Gas specific demand check fitting"
  },
  {
    "number": 221,
    "questionId": "b918de95-cca1-4bd6-9c40-e48f0f87c164",
    "question": "What term describes fittings that ensure gas is delivered as designated in medical systems?",
    "answer": "Check fitting"
  },
  {
    "number": 222,
    "questionId": "e1fc5c94-84a5-4b42-a3e3-3e1162f545ba",
    "question": "What action is not considered a basis for system breach?",
    "answer": "Alarm testing"
  },
  {
    "number": 223,
    "questionId": "a4734d7d-a41a-4914-a8be-62eb0dc0f624",
    "question": "What is the lowest temperature that nitrous oxide and carbon dioxide cylinders should be allowed to reach?",
    "answer": "20°F"
  },
  {
    "number": 224,
    "questionId": "482b9365-81f1-40bb-b606-790b95866187",
    "question": "Manufactured assemblies employing flexible hose shall have a minimum burst pressure of what PSI?",
    "answer": "1000"
  },
  {
    "number": 225,
    "questionId": "00bb3f24-35a7-44f7-afc1-517970484293",
    "question": "What type of gas is indicated for use when charging the system after determining no cross-connection?",
    "answer": "nitrogen NF"
  },
  {
    "number": 226,
    "questionId": "0643cc47-29a9-447b-a5e3-30c8ebb9043f",
    "question": "The maximum allowable concentration of particulate contaminants in instrument air is established to protect what?",
    "answer": "B) Patient safety"
  },
  {
    "number": 227,
    "questionId": "586dff6f-2e0c-473c-82b2-b1a0d25d2db8",
    "question": "Which condition is NOT alarmed in sources with standby headers?",
    "answer": "low discharge temperature"
  },
  {
    "number": 228,
    "questionId": "a5f49163-6a6e-4b2e-b26c-35ce8e75e4b0",
    "question": "Piping for category 3 positive-pressure medical gases shall be cleaned for oxygen service, delivered plugged or capped, and hard drawn, seamless copper ASTM _?",
    "answer": "B819"
  },
  {
    "number": 229,
    "questionId": "7c4e0524-60e0-44c3-9f53-058c4316aa4d",
    "question": "Factory installed inlet tubing on station outlets shall not be less than what NPS?",
    "answer": "1/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 230,
    "questionId": "adab85f2-527e-495c-8354-e4c90d7c24f5",
    "question": "When is it required to perform system blow down in medical gas systems?",
    "answer": "after initial installation"
  },
  {
    "number": 231,
    "questionId": "01ada077-da6a-4582-b8b1-256488113f33",
    "question": "What type of set of wires is permitted to connect a remote initiating device to a junction box?",
    "answer": "Single"
  },
  {
    "number": 232,
    "questionId": "a7af11d1-de76-4122-8e55-298690a5ad48",
    "question": "The installation of medical gas and vacuum systems shall be made by experienced, qualified, and competent installers. The installers shall meet the requirements of?",
    "answer": "ASSE standard 6010"
  },
  {
    "number": 233,
    "questionId": "5c0c3493-f02a-47f0-84d3-cad5d4bd2175",
    "question": "What happens if the medical air pressure decreases to an unacceptable level?",
    "answer": "The master alarm system activates"
  },
  {
    "number": 234,
    "questionId": "609be216-7692-4cd4-bc27-e6f208684fc8",
    "question": "The minimum NPS for drops to station outlets is?",
    "answer": "1/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 235,
    "questionId": "74fd0488-9a67-4d96-b5bf-7e2e8e441b99",
    "question": "A medical-surgical vacuum exhaust must be screened using which type of material?",
    "answer": "Any non-corroding"
  },
  {
    "number": 236,
    "questionId": "b1e19e63-041d-473e-80df-4c4dbe8d35e4",
    "question": "If more than one source equipment location exists, what type of alarms should be at the master panels?",
    "answer": "Master"
  },
  {
    "number": 237,
    "questionId": "fdaa9e59-ae58-4605-b30f-4e035530e0b1",
    "question": "Which of the following can be used for medical air if properly sealed?",
    "answer": "Reciprocating compressors"
  },
  {
    "number": 238,
    "questionId": "0319c459-7395-4665-ba19-abc656d40980",
    "question": "When does the master alarm system activate in a medical gas system supplied by a bulk system?",
    "answer": "When changeover occurs"
  },
  {
    "number": 239,
    "questionId": "4349e927-d60b-4500-96ce-3cf7e8a4a28b",
    "question": "What critical feature do medical air supply systems incorporate to ensure safety during operation?",
    "answer": "Redundant compressors"
  },
  {
    "number": 240,
    "questionId": "62aa0c75-ab88-4030-97b8-44ed411fd47d",
    "question": "Medical air shall be sampled upstream of which component?",
    "answer": "Source valve"
  },
  {
    "number": 241,
    "questionId": "fca636d4-4d76-4542-aee4-a4c5883a6634",
    "question": "The factory installed tuning on station outlets and inlets shall extend no further than how many inches from the body of the terminal?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "number": 242,
    "questionId": "81abfdaf-9284-425d-9692-402746a81f36",
    "question": "A medical-surgical vacuum receiver shall be made serviceable by which method?",
    "answer": "any method to ensure the continuation of service"
  },
  {
    "number": 243,
    "questionId": "64d46fe7-e0ec-4847-bf03-0d54a8acf3eb",
    "question": "What must be the status of outlet connections on gas containers when they are being removed?",
    "answer": "Functional"
  },
  {
    "number": 244,
    "questionId": "f07fb948-e705-485b-85b4-e3644acb5aed",
    "question": "Which of the following systems shall not be permitted to be located in an outdoor enclosure?",
    "answer": "Medical air sources"
  },
  {
    "number": 245,
    "questionId": "f2bb8f0b-aa6f-4e32-b7ac-2b0a297ed620",
    "question": "New or replacement valves are not required to be which type?",
    "answer": "ball type"
  },
  {
    "number": 246,
    "questionId": "57e1d6fc-a714-4b68-95b9-c97479603d24",
    "question": "Which of the following NPS is allowed for connecting tubing for alarms?",
    "answer": "1/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 247,
    "questionId": "b6d0c262-4d1c-49f5-a6e7-ccac34a976d2",
    "question": "Which type of gas shall not be used to power the venture of a WAGD system?",
    "answer": "Medical air"
  },
  {
    "number": 248,
    "questionId": "3cc448ba-1494-444c-bd2a-c695edefd138",
    "question": "Where should area alarm pressure sensors be installed in anesthetizing gas delivery areas?",
    "answer": "Source or patient"
  },
  {
    "number": 249,
    "questionId": "acf505f9-670a-42e9-a91c-62fe5b0c56c3",
    "question": "Alarm switches and sensors must be installed to ensure they are what?",
    "answer": "Removable"
  },
  {
    "number": 250,
    "questionId": "9a5292c1-d53b-469d-a365-317b55d4846c",
    "question": "An automatic means in a medical air compressor system is required to prevent what?",
    "answer": "Backflow"
  },
  {
    "number": 251,
    "questionId": "6ddb9c7a-749d-4525-88ba-6f614ea5b723",
    "question": "What is the main purpose of having a pressure relief valve in a medical gas system?",
    "answer": "B) To prevent system overpressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 252,
    "questionId": "f198f296-0a2d-49d6-84b3-7befa90db2b3",
    "question": "What is an incorrect assumption about medical gas pipeline systems?",
    "answer": "They can operate without relief valves"
  },
  {
    "number": 253,
    "questionId": "85097844-054d-4a50-b911-90ef95751e1e",
    "question": "Which component is essential for preventing backflow in a multi-pump vacuum system?",
    "answer": "Check valve"
  },
  {
    "number": 254,
    "questionId": "d2e57363-6370-434e-9463-a99733d8e45d",
    "question": "Cylinders in use and in storage shall be prevented from reaching temperatures in excess of what degree Fahrenheit?",
    "answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "number": 255,
    "questionId": "980ae343-940a-4488-96bd-270478fb6567",
    "question": "Factory installed outlet tubing on station inlets shall not be less than what NPS?",
    "answer": "3/8"
  },
  {
    "number": 256,
    "questionId": "aa12e698-8cdc-4f12-a613-f3c635bbb246",
    "question": "What feature should not be equipped on medical air receivers?",
    "answer": "A temperature indicator"
  },
  {
    "number": 257,
    "questionId": "547c66d3-b607-4ddf-9c07-09d0fe109c91",
    "question": "What minimum efficiency rating is required for medical air filters at 1 micron or greater?",
    "answer": "98%"
  },
  {
    "number": 258,
    "questionId": "9ccc00e1-d27e-4308-af2d-bdc97e978e1a",
    "question": "Intake air for instrument air compressors shall not be drawn from which source?",
    "answer": "C) medical air intake"
  },
  {
    "number": 259,
    "questionId": "f7208564-55b0-4a41-9c1b-87209550d47f",
    "question": "The vacuum exhaust must discharge a minimum of how many feet from any door, window, or air intake?",
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "number": 260,
    "questionId": "8281ad0e-35d4-42e5-958c-07cb0574695b",
    "question": "What are all brazed joints required to be examined for during the initial pressure test?",
    "answer": "leakage by means of a leak detectant safe for oxygen"
  },
  {
    "number": 261,
    "questionId": "8cf65923-06c4-4942-9c83-8d7e93f595d5",
    "question": "Runouts to alarm panels and connecting tubing for gauges and alarm devices shall be permitted to be which NPS?",
    "answer": "1/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 262,
    "questionId": "0c8acbaf-7ed0-4ec0-aca7-8a6ca6e82cd0",
    "question": "Which components are essential for the operation of central supply systems in a medical setting?",
    "answer": "Check valves and filters"
  },
  {
    "number": 263,
    "questionId": "bf710994-865f-4b8e-b15a-ccbbc2afe078",
    "question": "What is the purpose of the master alarm system in a medical gas setup?",
    "answer": "To signal changes in pressure or system faults"
  },
  {
    "number": 264,
    "questionId": "ea21355e-0e2b-4fb5-9f46-04dfc3e6505c",
    "question": "Locations for central supply systems shall have what type of devices protected from physical damage?",
    "answer": "Electrical"
  },
  {
    "number": 265,
    "questionId": "89f5d654-de2e-4642-ab5d-2980700ab13c",
    "question": "Which ASTM standard is NOT applicable to medical-surgical vacuum system piping made from hard-drawn seamless copper tube?",
    "answer": "ASTM B597"
  },
  {
    "number": 266,
    "questionId": "c8562121-3af7-46d0-bc0b-b4224acfd68f",
    "question": "Which document defines the qualifications for installers of medical gas systems?",
    "answer": "ASSE standard 6010"
  },
  {
    "number": 267,
    "questionId": "d6d9978d-4850-4014-91ff-6e7dfde25394",
    "question": "Station outlets that operate at a pressure in excess of what PSI shall be either D.I.S.S. or be designed to relieve pressure prior to removal of adapter?",
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "number": 268,
    "questionId": "42490394-872c-4140-a142-04999e3a77bc",
    "question": "Where should the emergency oxygen supply connection be placed when multiple buildings are served from a single cryogenic liquid oxygen source?",
    "answer": "Each building served"
  },
  {
    "number": 269,
    "questionId": "151e4aa8-2279-4bf8-a455-1baf54726c28",
    "question": "Where should medical air piping systems at different operating pressures separate?",
    "answer": "Filters"
  },
  {
    "number": 270,
    "questionId": "ff1b2396-1d87-4827-99da-608bd70b7ac2",
    "question": "Supports in damp locations must be?",
    "answer": "Plastic-coated"
  },
  {
    "number": 271,
    "questionId": "b9d32a65-3938-4608-a8a3-505664f05d7f",
    "question": "The responsible authority shall review the inspection and testing records prior to the use of all systems to ensure that all findings have been successfully completed. Who is this authority?",
    "answer": "responsible facility authority"
  },
  {
    "number": 272,
    "questionId": "635300a2-42cf-4ef4-87e0-d20e6cc429c5",
    "question": "What type of connectors shall be used to connect the vacuum pumps with their intake and outlet piping?",
    "answer": "flexible"
  },
  {
    "number": 273,
    "questionId": "d4a668f8-6794-4136-a77e-b04a098973f5",
    "question": "What is a function of the final line regulator in a medical air system?",
    "answer": "Monitors the pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 274,
    "questionId": "9768df2b-de27-4832-932a-1a51ee3cf25b",
    "question": "Who must furnish documentation certifying that all installed piping and materials are cleaned for oxygen service?",
    "answer": "Installer"
  },
  {
    "number": 275,
    "questionId": "929b48d7-21f9-4aff-844e-1ebbe394f4cd",
    "question": "What type of indicator is required for final line filters for instrument air to show the status of filter life?",
    "answer": "visual"
  },
  {
    "number": 276,
    "questionId": "66064e67-81d1-4505-9c83-c742f84435b6",
    "question": "Verification testing for medical gas and vacuum pipeline systems must meet the requirements of which standard?",
    "answer": "ASSE standard 6030"
  },
  {
    "number": 277,
    "questionId": "43e7469f-bb85-4e02-bbe4-88a234afe4d3",
    "question": "Medical air sources shall only be used for which application?",
    "answer": "Human respiratory applications"
  },
  {
    "number": 278,
    "questionId": "900fb9e6-3495-47f4-a642-94b234b86489",
    "question": "Which of the following is critical for the safe operation of medical gas systems regarding pressure levels?",
    "answer": "Monitoring at the source"
  },
  {
    "number": 279,
    "questionId": "2ad5be84-31ff-4803-a9f4-fa09a2d11a91",
    "question": "What type of alarm panel is permitted for category 2 warning systems?",
    "answer": "single"
  },
  {
    "number": 280,
    "questionId": "5ece5f46-322f-403f-8634-a741857c5bd3",
    "question": "What pressure drop in the medical-surgical vacuum system triggers the master alarm system?",
    "answer": "Any value below 12 in. HgV"
  },
  {
    "number": 281,
    "questionId": "22cf1344-c64f-47e8-9c6a-784fbd8f261c",
    "question": "Who must ensure that inspection and testing adhere to applicable provisions?",
    "answer": "documented procedure"
  },
  {
    "number": 282,
    "questionId": "c7e31f84-1790-4e68-924e-71259035a2b5",
    "question": "What does a signal from each local alarm system indicate at the master alarm panels?",
    "answer": "Source equipment issue is present"
  },
  {
    "number": 283,
    "questionId": "347458be-1511-4aea-a090-1c4780ad7235",
    "question": "Who is responsible for ensuring that fittings for positive pressure medical gas systems are cleaned for oxygen service before installation?",
    "answer": "Manufacturer"
  },
  {
    "number": 284,
    "questionId": "310e2719-fa8b-458e-86a1-f40948fbbd7e",
    "question": "Category 1 medical-surgical vacuum sources must consist of a minimum of how many vacuum pumps?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "number": 285,
    "questionId": "38c34004-8752-4919-a18b-df5f677381a1",
    "question": "The initial pressure test for positive pressure gases ensures that the system is tested to prevent what kind of issue?",
    "answer": "leakage"
  },
  {
    "number": 286,
    "questionId": "0d1a6ce0-1b36-4fa4-aba2-ddeefd404caf",
    "question": "Area alarms shall be tested to verify an alarm condition if the pressure in the piping system increases or decreases by what percentage?",
    "answer": "B) 20"
  },
  {
    "number": 287,
    "questionId": "015c2a66-7d69-422f-82fe-9b7a9bfeba1e",
    "question": "During a vacuum piping system test, a test pressure of 12 inches HgV is applied for how long?",
    "answer": "24 hours"
  },
  {
    "number": 288,
    "questionId": "655f36cd-a9b1-4fb7-9b11-50263b8d809e",
    "question": "How are manifold control systems maintained to ensure they operate effectively?",
    "answer": "Regular cleaning and inspection"
  },
  {
    "number": 289,
    "questionId": "d8941f59-b1ad-4974-85b0-cb30dac334bd",
    "question": "Where should the master alarm panel be located for the individual responsible for the maintenance of the medical gas piping system?",
    "answer": "Office or work space of the individual"
  },
  {
    "number": 290,
    "questionId": "5de768ca-0b2e-4d81-b82c-55af008e4668",
    "question": "Underground piping buried outside of buildings shall have an installation procedure to what while being backfilled?",
    "answer": "Protect"
  },
  {
    "number": 291,
    "questionId": "2cc00a34-84b8-4450-b8b0-9f105d28774d",
    "question": "Medical air compressors that are oil-based require what type of filter?",
    "answer": "Coalescing filters"
  },
  {
    "number": 292,
    "questionId": "f46d3113-7245-4928-8ee6-35ff57f6d203",
    "question": "What piping material is permitted for field-installed medical-surgical vacuum distribution systems?",
    "answer": "Stainless steel pipe"
  },
  {
    "number": 293,
    "questionId": "0cc7e804-ce5b-4202-a869-672c862b1986",
    "question": "What percentage indicates a pressure increase or decrease for area alarm panels in medical gas systems from normal operating pressure?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "number": 294,
    "questionId": "b224d669-0ea5-4886-b1e9-eaa561b0e59c",
    "question": "A low-pressure, vacuum insulated vessel containing gas in liquid form is called?",
    "answer": "container"
  },
  {
    "number": 295,
    "questionId": "592a0aaa-cd10-4e97-985e-fe74cc9d9ce5",
    "question": "What is the consequence if a brazer does not perform brazing for a duration exceeding 6 months?",
    "answer": "Qualifying period resets"
  },
  {
    "number": 296,
    "questionId": "2025a9a3-03c4-4dba-9505-b45580e7cc0d",
    "question": "All pressure relief valves shall be made of brass, bronze, or which other material?",
    "answer": "Stainless steel"
  },
  {
    "number": 297,
    "questionId": "646da960-4f72-4d14-9be5-13a45460ec68",
    "question": "The labeling shall be what for all components of the system?",
    "answer": "D) verified"
  },
  {
    "number": 298,
    "questionId": "3c66a1ec-31dc-40c7-aea1-e463e6da210c",
    "question": "What is the maximum allowable pressure for a vacuum source in dental systems?",
    "answer": "25 psi"
  },
  {
    "number": 299,
    "questionId": "1177150a-a3ff-4fcc-9899-6947743d4d71",
    "question": "Vacuum piping systems shall be subjected to a 24-hour standing test at a pressure between what measurement of HgV and full vacuum?",
    "answer": "12 in"
  },
  {
    "number": 300,
    "questionId": "45111e66-e42d-4b89-9f29-6737938506ce",
    "question": "How often should medical gas systems undergo testing for compliance and safety?",
    "answer": "A) Annually"
  },
  {
    "number": 301,
    "questionId": "7254f9dc-e922-4042-b1df-4c373502ce37",
    "question": "What is the minimum clearance around EOSC for a temporary source of supply?",
    "answer": "3 ft"
  },
  {
    "number": 302,
    "questionId": "2ea1a438-5428-4a03-bdc6-149c1326d750",
    "question": "Threaded joints shall be allowed on the source equipment on which side of the source valve?",
    "answer": "source"
  },
  {
    "number": 303,
    "questionId": "36945be4-d24c-4263-a969-f3329f5ba60d",
    "question": "A system shall be deemed breached as a result of all of the following except?",
    "answer": "alarm testing"
  },
  {
    "number": 304,
    "questionId": "71e6ea2c-f631-4011-9be2-0cdd015531bc",
    "question": "What is the scale range of vacuum indicators measured in inches of HgV?",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "number": 305,
    "questionId": "5d678db6-b5dc-4347-a794-bf4ca5299480",
    "question": "In what category is the loss of the piped gas and vacuum systems not likely to cause injury to patients, staff, or visitors, but can cause discomfort?",
    "answer": "category 3"
  },
  {
    "number": 306,
    "questionId": "87784ff7-1652-402e-b242-562cecc3b7c8",
    "question": "Cylinders in use must not exceed a temperature of which specified degree Fahrenheit?",
    "answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "number": 307,
    "questionId": "e3bf403e-7ded-49c2-9e7d-b11331423b39",
    "question": "What is the maximum permitted interval for spacing pipe labels?",
    "answer": "20 feet"
  },
  {
    "number": 308,
    "questionId": "1189f2d7-59b8-45fc-81ab-5ab371d70011",
    "question": "A shutoff valve shall be placed at the immediate connection of each source system to what type of system?",
    "answer": "source"
  },
  {
    "number": 309,
    "questionId": "732d61ac-02a2-4898-ac78-0078542f22ea",
    "question": "What should aftercoolers be provided with?",
    "answer": "Flexible connectors"
  },
  {
    "number": 310,
    "questionId": "d69ed1ff-885e-4973-bd3c-e7c0bb3a3e64",
    "question": "What kind of indicators shall all master, area, and local alarm systems include for each condition monitored?",
    "answer": "Visual, audible"
  },
  {
    "number": 311,
    "questionId": "fc970ed7-5b34-4288-bb98-8831de2b0002",
    "question": "A category 3 moisture indicator shall indicate when the relative humidity of the dental air exceeds _ at line pressure and temperature?",
    "answer": "40%"
  },
  {
    "number": 312,
    "questionId": "01e33b41-9bb3-44ee-a1cd-6e8adf94e8dd",
    "question": "What type of signal is required to indicate the operating status of manifolds for gas cylinders?",
    "answer": "Local"
  },
  {
    "number": 313,
    "questionId": "22807c58-2d60-4508-b6d4-4d6e493c8c94",
    "question": "Why is it important for the master alarm panel to be monitored continuously?",
    "answer": "To ensure rapid response to any issues"
  },
  {
    "number": 314,
    "questionId": "511067b8-700e-461b-a1b1-2bd83c5b4ca5",
    "question": "Which valves allow modification of lateral branch piping from a main or riser without shutting down the entire main, riser, or facility?",
    "answer": "service"
  },
  {
    "number": 315,
    "questionId": "8db4c9a8-0e47-4915-be70-7da670e3b17b",
    "question": "Which of the following filler metals shall be used to braze copper-to-copper joints in medical gas and vacuum distribution piping?",
    "answer": "BCuP series"
  },
  {
    "number": 316,
    "questionId": "5b4941ce-1535-42a7-ab08-3dacd444c3ce",
    "question": "A continuous tape or marker placed immediately above the buried pipe must clearly identify the pipeline by what?",
    "answer": "Specific name"
  },
  {
    "number": 317,
    "questionId": "880d341a-9fa1-409c-9daf-543faba1a895",
    "question": "For brazed joints, which temperature in degrees Fahrenheit must the melting temperature of the brazing alloy exceed to maintain piping integrity in a fire?",
    "answer": "1000"
  },
  {
    "number": 318,
    "questionId": "c2370859-876f-4cf2-8afe-5509888d1085",
    "question": "What purpose do alarm systems serve in medical gas installations?",
    "answer": "Monitor conditions"
  },
  {
    "number": 319,
    "questionId": "37f8aaeb-4db3-4809-9a35-0319c42b179d",
    "question": "Piping shall be labeled by?",
    "answer": "stenciling or adhesive markers"
  },
  {
    "number": 320,
    "questionId": "af92fe83-e055-49aa-b080-4b79bab0b687",
    "question": "Which type of gas is not allowed to be stored outdoors according to safety regulations?",
    "answer": "Medical air"
  },
  {
    "number": 321,
    "questionId": "7c837d4c-fbaa-438f-b745-e20253d9bd48",
    "question": "When using the autogenous orbital welding process, joints shall be continuously what inside and outside with inert gas as qualified with a procedure?",
    "answer": "purged"
  },
  {
    "number": 322,
    "questionId": "1a0118dc-63d8-432e-8680-fab0bb6c50c7",
    "question": "Inspection and testing shall be performed on all new piped gas systems to ensure all applicable provisions have been adhered to and system integrity has been achieved or maintained through a?",
    "answer": "documented procedure"
  },
  {
    "number": 323,
    "questionId": "fd1a5eb6-5029-4d8c-84d7-2da700d9e32f",
    "question": "Which type of compressor can introduce oil into the medical air system if not configured correctly?",
    "answer": "Reciprocating compressors"
  },
  {
    "number": 324,
    "questionId": "3b2ad379-2250-4cfc-8caa-6e6db409a246",
    "question": "Drops to individual station outlets and inlets shall not be less than which NPS?",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "number": 325,
    "questionId": "d7c587a3-fa75-49e1-84d2-901d3809167a",
    "question": "What qualification is required to install a category 2 medical gas system?",
    "answer": "ASSE 6010"
  },
  {
    "number": 326,
    "questionId": "92288a18-6d7b-41c0-9f7c-2a3564e87783",
    "question": "In what category is the loss of piped gas likely to cause minor injury?",
    "answer": "category 2"
  },
  {
    "number": 327,
    "questionId": "28baada5-1a31-4953-bd26-804b7419ad3d",
    "question": "A standard gauge pressure of 160-185 psi applies to which of the following?",
    "answer": "instrument air"
  },
  {
    "number": 328,
    "questionId": "24262dde-0d9a-495c-956c-3d65700a1293",
    "question": "What is the acceptable accuracy range of digital indicators as a percentage of the operating pressure?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "number": 329,
    "questionId": "8af7fcca-4199-493b-a4ad-f01be40befd0",
    "question": "In patient care areas, medical gas piping must comply with which of the following requirements?",
    "answer": "Avoid open flame areas"
  },
  {
    "number": 330,
    "questionId": "8584b907-6fd8-47c9-89ae-2267220a4646",
    "question": "Who shall conduct the verification testing?",
    "answer": "a party other than the installing contractor"
  },
  {
    "number": 331,
    "questionId": "68504129-3a3f-4b4e-b601-f6b4ce170e3f",
    "question": "The initial pressure test for positive pressure gases and vacuum systems shall have a test pressure of 1.5 times the system working pressure, but not less than what PSI?",
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "number": 332,
    "questionId": "988297bb-e276-4210-8640-a33ce0f8e99d",
    "question": "What is the minimum distance for the medical air intake from all doors, windows, or other openings in a building?",
    "answer": "10 ft"
  },
  {
    "number": 333,
    "questionId": "46f5dd0f-3d1c-4980-9273-3203213668de",
    "question": "The minimum backfilled cover above the top of the pipe or its enclosure shall be 36 inches, except that the minimum cover shall be permitted to be reduced to how many inches where there is no potential damage from surface loads or surface conditions?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "number": 334,
    "questionId": "b937cfc9-8f30-430c-96e1-ffe2a6c4d18d",
    "question": "Cylinder and cryogenic liquid container outlet connections shall be designed as to render the attachment point unusable when removal of the outlet connection is attempted. What is the intended design outcome?",
    "answer": "Unusable"
  },
  {
    "number": 335,
    "questionId": "d04020bb-4bd4-4f11-b08f-7336bc819ba1",
    "question": "What should be monitored to ensure safe operation of medical air systems?",
    "answer": "Pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 336,
    "questionId": "54b0c4d1-4e32-427a-8751-1fb864548914",
    "question": "What type of shutoff valve shall be provided in the main supply line when the source valve is inaccessible from within the building?",
    "answer": "main"
  },
  {
    "number": 337,
    "questionId": "cc54b8dd-86ba-430d-86bf-27b99d07d507",
    "question": "What type of audible indication should all medical gas alarm systems have for each condition monitored?",
    "answer": "Cancelable"
  },
  {
    "number": 338,
    "questionId": "badb5f2b-222e-455b-b69a-74531b19e854",
    "question": "Medical air receivers must allow for what during service?",
    "answer": "Being filled"
  },
  {
    "number": 339,
    "questionId": "b4638763-e7bb-4d4e-8970-cff1992b334a",
    "question": "What type of valves shall be readily operable from a standing position in the corridor on the same floor they serve?",
    "answer": "zone"
  },
  {
    "number": 340,
    "questionId": "d8d87af7-141a-4936-b68f-41652911e1bd",
    "question": "What is the required relief setting for valves in central supply systems for positive pressure gases above normal working operating pressure?",
    "answer": "50%"
  },
  {
    "number": 341,
    "questionId": "d6f48cef-fd12-474f-a4e5-64b6bf4b8a1a",
    "question": "Where category 3 medical gas supply systems supply two treatment facilities, each facility shall be provided with an emergency _ valve?",
    "answer": "shutoff"
  },
  {
    "number": 342,
    "questionId": "41753799-9ec2-4ae0-89cc-cd044b1c7146",
    "question": "A medical-surgical vacuum system should always aim to minimize what?",
    "answer": "Back pressure"
  },
  {
    "number": 343,
    "questionId": "75cacf2e-8cc2-42f9-935b-baf6113361b7",
    "question": "Liquids drained from a category 3 vacuum source shall discharge _ to a sanitary drainage system?",
    "answer": "indirectly"
  },
  {
    "number": 344,
    "questionId": "b1c194f4-0d19-4639-8171-550263c47edd",
    "question": "Which valves should not be located in a room with station outlets or inlets that they control?",
    "answer": "zone"
  },
  {
    "number": 345,
    "questionId": "fdccbfeb-e015-45fc-8bfd-5d85f5883bc1",
    "question": "What should be included in the auxiliary source connection for a medical gas system?",
    "answer": "Valves"
  },
  {
    "number": 346,
    "questionId": "676bcd6f-d5a9-441e-b6bc-ca0aba928afa",
    "question": "What type of material is recommended for the piping of category 3 medical gases?",
    "answer": "seamless copper"
  },
  {
    "number": 347,
    "questionId": "500cc72b-cfc0-49a2-b17c-88613c3c0b0e",
    "question": "Station outlets and inlets of manufactured assemblies that employ hose or flexible connections to the piping system that are not fully and immediately accessible shall use what type of connectors?",
    "answer": "D.I.S.S."
  },
  {
    "number": 348,
    "questionId": "386165b4-2738-4b2f-9187-35561e9fd2b4",
    "question": "Pressure relief valves for dental air systems having less than _ ft3 at STP shall be permitted to discharge locally indoors?",
    "answer": "3000"
  },
  {
    "number": 349,
    "questionId": "7c568f95-a485-4592-b9b4-50c60facfd2c",
    "question": "Pipe labels shall be located at intervals of not more than how many feet?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "number": 350,
    "questionId": "2cd72efc-8fa3-4553-8bfe-436f9f76eb98",
    "question": "In-line check valves are not required to have what feature?",
    "answer": "threaded end connections"
  },
  {
    "number": 351,
    "questionId": "e222fe84-aa21-40ec-bf4f-9b6e4840a1a4",
    "question": "What percentage of the zones shall be tested at the outlet most remote from the source by the verifier to complete the piping particulate test?",
    "answer": "A) 25"
  },
  {
    "number": 352,
    "questionId": "fb92503a-adf2-4939-9c8c-dd585ca45496",
    "question": "Where instrument air systems are provided with a standby header, the header shall have how many cylinders attached?",
    "answer": "A) a sufficient amount for one hour of normal operation"
  },
  {
    "number": 353,
    "questionId": "fbe0070e-69a6-4682-b21f-defd98ac828b",
    "question": "Outdoor locations surrounded by impermeable walls, except fire barrier walls, shall have protected ventilation openings at what part of each wall?",
    "answer": "Base"
  },
  {
    "number": 354,
    "questionId": "21b115b9-117e-477b-9612-45c4ad06b3d3",
    "question": "What should a medical air compressor system's pressure relief valve be set at above line pressure?",
    "answer": "50 percent"
  },
  {
    "number": 355,
    "questionId": "9c9ff3ad-912b-4988-b984-1017434fd1d6",
    "question": "What type of alarm activates to indicate the operation of the backup compressor in an instrument air source?",
    "answer": "local"
  },
  {
    "number": 356,
    "questionId": "37c40592-fec9-4028-b780-72fea45a3549",
    "question": "Joints shall be brazed within how many hours after surfaces are cleaned for brazing?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "number": 357,
    "questionId": "c3169618-9d5f-4555-9a5e-049ccdc1147a",
    "question": "Performance qualification of brazers shall remain in effect indefinitely unless the brazer does not braze with the qualified procedure for a period exceeding how many months?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "number": 358,
    "questionId": "e500646a-5abf-41e4-95b5-9350a39278ff",
    "question": "Nitrous oxide and carbon dioxide using cylinders or portable containers shall be prevented from reaching temperatures lower than what degree Fahrenheit?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "number": 359,
    "questionId": "205e1828-2870-4ff2-9280-1705d03a2e18",
    "question": "The scale range of positive pressure analog indicators shall have the normal operating pressure fall within which part of the gauge scale?",
    "answer": "Middle third"
  },
  {
    "number": 360,
    "questionId": "43525e1a-636f-4318-848b-d5e8de9da742",
    "question": "What type of indicator is required for coalescing filters in oil-employing medical air compressors?",
    "answer": "An element change"
  },
  {
    "number": 361,
    "questionId": "e3dd60bd-c1d2-4546-a6c2-c400471e7796",
    "question": "All positive pressure supply systems shall be provided with duplex line pressure regulators piped in which configuration?",
    "answer": "Parallel"
  },
  {
    "number": 362,
    "questionId": "41d7af66-3f5e-4290-b8a7-e8f2220e3a02",
    "question": "Mains and branches in medical gas piping systems shall be not less than which NPS?",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "number": 363,
    "questionId": "c4908317-5d02-4534-ad91-23604582a020",
    "question": "Which type of oxygen system location is generally prohibited from having access to open flame areas?",
    "answer": "Indoor"
  },
  {
    "number": 364,
    "questionId": "d8aeb6d5-9ab7-4a1d-a860-944ff171f333",
    "question": "Each station outlet/inlet for medical gases and vacuums shall be what type?",
    "answer": "gas-specific"
  },
  {
    "number": 365,
    "questionId": "8672e109-6fb9-4dd9-9d0b-442dfd8afae1",
    "question": "Regardless of how many zone valve boxes are installed on a lateral branch off a riser, only one what type of valve is required for each branch?",
    "answer": "service"
  },
  {
    "number": 366,
    "questionId": "f0eafad8-d237-439e-9b31-43aed4bc4129",
    "question": "What is the test gas used by the installer?",
    "answer": "Nitrogen NF"
  },
  {
    "number": 367,
    "questionId": "4eb95a58-42f5-4fda-b67e-777a9413f5a7",
    "question": "Piping between the vacuum pump and the source shutoff valve shall not be made of which material?",
    "answer": "plastic (PVC)"
  },
  {
    "number": 368,
    "questionId": "35280c97-3ce1-4ef1-b1c2-b84e473d23b7",
    "question": "In a vacuum exhaust system, which of the following cannot be used to isolate the pumps?",
    "answer": "Grooved joint"
  },
  {
    "number": 369,
    "questionId": "d72e1626-7ee1-4c4b-983a-530e0a29eadf",
    "question": "What can substitute one of the alarm panels in a master alarm system?",
    "answer": "Centralized computer system"
  },
  {
    "number": 370,
    "questionId": "27b181fc-c5ae-47ce-9d8e-d5e518f5a7ac",
    "question": "Additional WAGD producers shall activate how when the operating producer fails to maintain required vacuum?",
    "answer": "Automatically"
  },
  {
    "number": 371,
    "questionId": "e1fc5c94-84a5-4b42-a3e3-3e1162f545ba",
    "question": "What action is not considered a basis for system breach?",
    "answer": "Alarm testing"
  },
  {
    "number": 372,
    "questionId": "2372f5bf-8002-4c10-8002-e43fd1dad504",
    "question": "In potentially damp locations, hangers or supports that are in contact with the tube shall be what or otherwise electrically insulated from the tube?",
    "answer": "Plastic-coated"
  },
  {
    "number": 373,
    "questionId": "9a5b464c-9a5f-483a-9751-18ade98b09cc",
    "question": "At what dew point temperature does the medical air dew point high alarm activate?",
    "answer": "+35°F"
  },
  {
    "number": 374,
    "questionId": "04f6ba84-ecd1-40a6-bec8-25f4982584be",
    "question": "Category 2 medical-surgical vacuum systems are permitted to be what configuration?",
    "answer": "simplex"
  },
  {
    "number": 375,
    "questionId": "603ab9f5-7641-4b9a-b314-042b547ae00c",
    "question": "Nfpa 99 requires tubing to be cut using a sharp tubing cutter that shall be free from grease, oil, and other lubricants not suitable for oxygen service. After cutting, tubing ends shall be permitted to be?",
    "answer": "rolled smooth or deburred"
  },
  {
    "number": 376,
    "questionId": "80bcc0f9-5c76-4980-864d-120256495831",
    "question": "At what parts per million (ppm) do local alarms activate for high carbon monoxide levels in a medical air system?",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "number": 377,
    "questionId": "a5f49163-6a6e-4b2e-b26c-35ce8e75e4b0",
    "question": "Piping for category 3 positive-pressure medical gases shall be cleaned for oxygen service, delivered plugged or capped, and hard drawn, seamless copper ASTM _?",
    "answer": "B819"
  },
  {
    "number": 378,
    "questionId": "3ee31404-2656-43be-81ec-85fdfd36fa9b",
    "question": "Which standard is NOT a requirement for the quality of medical air?",
    "answer": "Be filtered to .01 microns"
  },
  {
    "number": 379,
    "questionId": "e184268a-ebe7-47b6-86b2-0fc0661d2926",
    "question": "Which of the following does NOT represent an indicator in the alarm system?",
    "answer": "Mock signal"
  },
  {
    "number": 380,
    "questionId": "c8e128a9-f317-40f0-b9d7-a2ae3d5b1aaf",
    "question": "In a vacuum system, what occurs when not enough vacuum is maintained?",
    "answer": "Air entry"
  },
  {
    "number": 381,
    "questionId": "e1fcc402-a5fe-4f1a-a3e9-209a1a345d82",
    "question": "The manufacturer is allowed a decay of less than what percentage in 24 hours during the standing pressure test?",
    "answer": "1.0"
  },
  {
    "number": 382,
    "questionId": "7837acc4-9022-45ae-b002-6a55cda1b269",
    "question": "What treatment is required for water used in liquid ring compressors to prevent pathogens and chlorine?",
    "answer": "Hypochlorination"
  },
  {
    "number": 383,
    "questionId": "8850a6b1-1e15-4982-8a8b-86f1938799eb",
    "question": "WAGD producers designed for operation at vacuums below how many inches of HgV shall only be used for WAGD service?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "number": 384,
    "questionId": "9411e0b2-fca4-4cc7-839b-492dbe94a6c2",
    "question": "What is the initial pressure test pressure for a category 2 system?",
    "answer": "1.5 but not less than 150 psi"
  },
  {
    "number": 385,
    "questionId": "58432740-796f-444d-a6d2-47a6a828f6fa",
    "question": "Axially swaged fittings that provide a metal to metal seal having pressure and temperature ratings of a brazed joint when complete are?",
    "answer": "permanent"
  },
  {
    "number": 386,
    "questionId": "00bb3f24-35a7-44f7-afc1-517970484293",
    "question": "What type of gas is indicated for use when charging the system after determining no cross-connection?",
    "answer": "nitrogen NF"
  },
  {
    "number": 387,
    "questionId": "a74ccb87-761f-4ddc-b012-e302bf1245f5",
    "question": "Who shall provide documentation certifying the performance and successful completion of all pressure testing for a manufactured assembly?",
    "answer": "manufacturer"
  },
  {
    "number": 388,
    "questionId": "586dff6f-2e0c-473c-82b2-b1a0d25d2db8",
    "question": "Which condition is NOT alarmed in sources with standby headers?",
    "answer": "low discharge temperature"
  },
  {
    "number": 389,
    "questionId": "482b9365-81f1-40bb-b606-790b95866187",
    "question": "Manufactured assemblies employing flexible hose shall have a minimum burst pressure of what PSI?",
    "answer": "1000"
  },
  {
    "number": 390,
    "questionId": "a4b38e60-a9de-4ae9-9e90-be2d4a172e3d",
    "question": "How many seals must separate the oil-containing section from the compression chamber in reciprocating compressors for medical air?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "number": 391,
    "questionId": "1bf5ad9f-22fe-446b-88eb-57ec25ef390a",
    "question": "Mains and branches in medical-surgical vacuum systems shall not be less than which NPS?",
    "answer": "3/4"
  },
  {
    "number": 392,
    "questionId": "bff9e90b-81bc-4e0b-aa69-48de9ac6460b",
    "question": "What is the purpose of performing a standing pressure test?",
    "answer": "Ensure system integrity"
  },
  {
    "number": 393,
    "questionId": "6b576d1d-4983-4d27-8226-d12abbfa7801",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a requirement for the quality of instrument air?",
    "answer": "A) dry to a dew point of 35*F"
  },
  {
    "number": 394,
    "questionId": "c784a886-eb27-4e3e-8ef5-e1f7899f83bb",
    "question": "Who must witness a 24-hour standing pressure test?",
    "answer": "designee of the authority having jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    "number": 395,
    "questionId": "ca8f715d-86c7-423d-8a91-0c53adecfcc8",
    "question": "How many connections should manifolds for gas cylinders have at a minimum?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "number": 396,
    "questionId": "07063fc8-f3da-4ebb-bce0-e6932632d7a5",
    "question": "When the dew point at system pressure exceeds what temperature in Fahrenheit, an alarm is activated?",
    "answer": "-22"
  },
  {
    "number": 397,
    "questionId": "9a9fd8ae-2496-4fc2-b846-a3fdd94628f9",
    "question": "When should the dew point monitor activate alarms in the medical air system?",
    "answer": "When dew point exceeds 35°F"
  },
  {
    "number": 398,
    "questionId": "517a88cc-671b-4d24-872a-3136848a960b",
    "question": "A Category 1 dedicated WAGD source must consist of how many producers to serve the peak calculated demand?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "number": 399,
    "questionId": "74fd0488-9a67-4d96-b5bf-7e2e8e441b99",
    "question": "A medical-surgical vacuum exhaust must be screened using which type of material?",
    "answer": "Any non-corroding"
  },
  {
    "number": 400,
    "questionId": "5fafa9bd-a854-4933-8571-453a338e8a42",
    "question": "When multiple vacuum pumps are joined to a common exhaust, the common exhaust must be sized to achieve what?",
    "answer": "Minimize back pressure"
  }
]